Like is just a
means to an end
We are at a
of like humanity's evolution
now that technology is
mainstream right Any age
group mother grandmother everyone
is connected to technology
and seeing like productivity
yield right So to
the extent that Southeast
Asia all of us
can actually take these
weapons of productivity these
of creation and kind
of arm everyone from
the villages all the
way to the you
can see a time
where capitalism is actually
doing more good than
ever right So I
really appreciate all of
you having me on
the show and like
talking a about these
things but I just
want to leave like
the with that thought
right Like we're not
here just to kind
and make billion dollar
that's just besides the
Behind every single funding
round there are like
and billions of beneficiaries
Like even a company
like is so many
drivers and so many
folks who are in
gig economy and so
much additional income So
if we can make
this new economy the
most inclusive economy the
world has ever seen
like that's the job
that we need to
do